Inventory of the V. M. Zubok interviews
Hoover Institution Archives
V. M. Zubok interviews
1989-2000
2013C16
Hoover Institution Archives
1 cardfile box (0.4 linear feet)
Sound recordings of interviews of Soviet and American government officials, relating to Soviet foreign policy during the presidency of Mikhail Gorbachev.
Zubok, V. M. (Vladislav Martinovich), interviewer.
Access
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. Use copies of some sound recordings, video recordings, or motion picture material in this collection are available for immediate access. To listen to other sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 2013.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Scope and Content of Collection
Sound recordings of interviews of Soviet and American government officials, relating to Soviet foreign policy during the presidency of Mikhail Gorbachev.
Audiotapes.; Soviet Union--Foreign relations--1985-1991.
- 1989 sound recording (Box 1)
  Access
  Use copy reference number: 2013c16_a_0008925
- 1989 sound recording in English (Box 1)
  Use copy reference number: 2013c16_a_0008928
- 1990 sound recording (Box 1)
  Use copy reference number: 2013c16_a_0008926
- 1993 sound recording (Box 1)
  Use copy reference number: 2013c16_a_0008920
- 20 Jul 1993 (Box 1)
  Use copy reference number: 2013c16_a_0008915
- 25 Mar 1999 sound recordings (Box 1)
  Use copy reference number: 2013c16_a_0008921
- 27 Jun 1989 sound recording (Box 1)
  Use copy reference number: 2013c16_a_0008929
- 28 Jul 1999 sound recording (Box 1)
  Use copy reference number: 2013c16_a_0008922
- 31 May 1989 and 06 Jun 1989 sound recordings (Box 1)
  Use copy reference number: 2013c16_a_0008931
- Konus 1990 (Box 1)
  Use copy reference number: 2013c16_a_0008914
- Robert Zoellick interview on 1 Mar 2000 (Box 1)
  Use copy reference number: 2013c16_a_0008932